<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
  <guestbook_post>
    <name>Elke Neubauer</name>
    <email>el.neubauer.en@gmail.com</email>
    <title>Himmlisch</title>
    <post>Danke fuer die wunderschoene Zeit im Hibiscus, wir kommen bestimmt wieder. Happy new year and best regards to Tom and Jerry.</post>
    <date>1640981350</date>
  </guestbook_post>
  <guestbook_post>
    <name>Soorej Munraj</name>
    <email>smunraj@gmail.com</email>
    <title>excellent</title>
    <post>Excellent moment passé en famille pour l'anniversaire de mon épouse. La vue et l'emplacement de l'hotel sont tout simplement splendides!! Excellent service et le carry de poisson suprême. Déjeuner et voir les reflets de l'eau sont tout bonnement appaisants! J'y retournerais pour sur!</post>
    <date>1597655220</date>
  </guestbook_post>
  <guestbook_post>
    <name>Soorej Munraj</name>
    <email>smunraj@gmail.com</email>
    <title>Excellent!!</title>
    <post>Excellent moment passé en famille pour l'anniversaire de mon épouse. La vue et l'emplacement de l'hotel sont tout simplement splendides!! Excellent service et le carry de poisson suprême. Déjeuner et voir les reflets de l'eau sont tout bonnement appaisants! J'y retournerais pour sur!</post>
    <date>1597655186</date>
  </guestbook_post>
  <guestbook_post>
    <name>Parisha Haton</name>
    <email>parishahaton@gmail.com</email>
    <title>Thank You</title>
    <post>Dear Hibiscus team,&#13;
&#13;
Sorry for the late review, but better late than never. We are a Mauritian family who stayed at your hotel on the 1st of Feb 2020. And it was very good, thank you. From the lady who took my reservation, the gentleman at the gate, the lady who welcomed us at the reception, the gentleman at the restaurant, the amazing breakfast lady, the comfort of the room, the sega show, it was all AMAZING. Thank you for your hospitality. Keep up the good work!</post>
    <date>1582023059</date>
  </guestbook_post>
  <guestbook_post>
    <name>Raffetseder Andrea</name>
    <email>a.raffetseder@aon.at</email>
    <title>Wunderbarer Urlaub</title>
    <post>Ich kann dieses Hotel nur empfehlen! Das Personal sehr bemüht freundlich! Ich hatte echt einen tollen erholsamen Urlaub! Werde nächstes Jahr wieder kommen! Lg Andrea Raffetseder</post>
    <date>1581612555</date>
  </guestbook_post>
  <guestbook_post>
    <name>Andrea Raffetseder</name>
    <email>a.raffetseder@aon.at</email>
    <title>Fantastischer Urlaub</title>
    <post>Ich war vom 28.01.20 - 11.02.2020 in diesem tollen Hotel! Es war für mich so ein erholsamer Urlaub! Das Personal soo bemüht und freundlich! :-) Werde das ganz bestimmt weiter empfehlen! Werde nächstes Jahr wieder kommen! Glg Andrea Raffetseder</post>
    <date>1581612444</date>
  </guestbook_post>
  <guestbook_post>
    <name>Eric Larose</name>
    <email>elarose2008@live.nl</email>
    <title>Reference</title>
    <post>Very Nice hotel,the service and the personal in the restaurant is marvellous.they are very gentle.specially Permal he's a very good guy.fixed everything for us compliment About it.and certainly we Will come back here.100 percent!</post>
    <date>1493455657</date>
  </guestbook_post>
  <guestbook_post>
    <name>couple from sweden</name>
    <email>indamoney23@hotmail.com</email>
    <title>Wonderful hotel with friendly people</title>
    <post>My wife and I had had an unforgetable stay in this chraming hotel. We had a big and nice rum with a jacuzzi with a balcony facing the ocean. What more can you ask for? And how could we forget Vikash , our driver and guide who really did everything he could to guide to please us. The same thoughts go to the nice guy at the reception which I dont remember the name but was the one who upgrade us to a suite and introduced us to Vikash. If you are staying at their hotel the 2 guys are the people to talk to. But evrybody else was just as nice.</post>
    <date>1470138689</date>
  </guestbook_post>
  <guestbook_post>
    <name>Ahmed</name>
    <email>indamoney23@hotmail.com</email>
    <title>Wonderful hotel with friendly people</title>
    <post>My wife and I had had an unforgetable stay in this chraming hotel. We had a big and nice rum with a jacuzzi with a balcony facing the ocean. What more can you ask for? We had many beaches just a few minutes walk away and the super market winners just 5 minutes away. The hotel is surrounded by plenty of restaurant that offer great food at a cheap price. And how could we forget Vikash , our driver and guide who really did everything he could to guide us and help us during our hourney, the same thoughts go to the nice guy at the reception which I dont remember the name but was the one who upgrade us to a suite and introduced us to Vikash. If you are staying at their hotel the 2 guys are the people to talk to. But evrybody else was just as nice, the restaurant staff, the house keeping the massage girl, the secutiry etc...</post>
    <date>1470137591</date>
  </guestbook_post>
  <guestbook_post>
    <name>Caleb Pearce</name>
    <email>pearce.caleb@gmail.com</email>
    <title>Wonderful setting!</title>
    <post>Thank you Irene for providing us with a never-to-be forgotten holiday. We cannot find superlatives to trump those that have already been mentioned. From the first moment to the last we received  superb hospitality. We would love to come back again.</post>
    <date>1443430601</date>
  </guestbook_post>
  <guestbook_post>
    <name>Richard</name>
    <email>r@int.mu</email>
    <title>Sir</title>
    <post>wonderful RESORT, ABSOLUTELY MAGNIFICENT , THANK YOU ALL FOR MAKNG MY STAY SO WONDERFUL</post>
    <date>1414992499</date>
  </guestbook_post>
  <guestbook_post>
    <name>Olivia Stephens</name>
    <email>stephensj01@btconnect.com</email>
    <title>lovely holiday August 2014</title>
    <post>We stayed at Garbis villas in August 2014 with our two children, aged 12 and 9. We loved it! The accommodation was great - very comfortable and good air conditioning! Beautiful pool and amazing sea views. Hope to return to Kefalonia again soon. Thanks, Irene, for such a wonderful time...xxx</post>
    <date>1409335308</date>
  </guestbook_post>
  <guestbook_post>
    <name>shivani rathore</name>
    <email>shivani@kimberliteindia.com</email>
    <title>summer vacation - April - May 2014.</title>
    <post>Ashish, Karan, Aryan and myself had a wonderful stay at the resort. Great place, great food and great staff. </post>
    <date>1405418987</date>
  </guestbook_post>
  <guestbook_post>
    <name>DEURVEILHER Didier</name>
    <email>deurveilher_didier@yahoo.fr</email>
    <title>Un petit coucou de la Réunion</title>
    <post>Un petit coucou à toute l'équipe de l'hôtel Hibiscus. En vacance à l'hôtel du 18 février au 1er mars 2013, j'ai été conquis par l'accueil, le service et la nourriture. J'ai trouvé la chambre vraiment bien avec un service de nettoyage tous les jours. Toutes le personnes travaillant à l'hôtel sont très disponibles et vous conseillent et vous informent au mieux en cas de besoin. Pour moi c'est sûr, je reviendrai avec beaucoup de plaisir dans cet hôtel.&#13;
A toute l'équipe je souhaite une bonne continuation et surtout ne changez rien.&#13;
&#13;
Ah oui j'oubliais, le spa est fantastique</post>
    <date>1362312799</date>
  </guestbook_post>
  <guestbook_post>
    <name>Joe</name>
    <email>gui_poigneur@hotmail.com</email>
    <title>Mari top</title>
    <post>Un hotel a conseille a tout le monde. Le plus jolie jardin qu'un hotel puisse avoir et n'en parlons pas de la vue. Bravo a tous.</post>
    <date>1355828770</date>
  </guestbook_post>
  <guestbook_post>
    <name>J.H Sosef</name>
    <email>j.sosef@hotmail.com</email>
    <title>Super</title>
    <post>Prima schoon hotel, mooie ruime kamers. Prachtig privestrandje in sfeervolle omgeving, vele restaurantjes op loopafstand maar maaltijden in hotel zijn ook prima. Kortom aanrader.</post>
    <date>1355673228</date>
  </guestbook_post>
</root>
